Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art rental records, 1961-1973 COR0003.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art rental records
1961-1973
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art
COR0003.1.RG
9 Linear Feet 6 record center cartons
The Art Rental and Sales Gallery operated from March 9, 1962 to 1973. The Rental Gallery was designed to offer Corcoran members original works of art on a rental basis for private homes, as well as for corporate offices, and to introduce Washingtonians to current American and local artists. The records of the Art Rental and Sales Gallery include consignments with commercial galleries and individual artists, master contracts, prospective artist records, inventories and shipping lists, correspondence, rental procedures, administrative information and operating procedures, financial reports, insurance, legal information and suits, rental applications and agreements, and Gallery income reports from rentals and sales.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
Series 2 Subseries 12 Legal problems and suits may contain materials with restricted content. All requests to use materials in Series 2 Subseries 12 must be reviewed and approved by the Public Services Librarian.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 3 series: Consignments, Administration, and Rental and sales.
Historical narrative
This history was prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities.
The Art Rental and Sales Gallery opened March 9, 1962 in gallery 42. The Rental Gallery was designed to offer Corcoran members original works of art on a two-month rental basis for private homes, as well as for corporate offices. A collection of works by contemporary American artists was selected on a consignment basis principally from commercial galleries in New York and Washington; although in some cases, consignments were arranged directly with the artist.
For the first five years of the Rental Gallery, Washington area interior designers created a series of room displays each Fall and Spring. The intention was to give prospective renters a chance to view contemporary works of art in home and office settings. In the spring of 1967, the Art Rental Gallery was moved to the rear of the building adjacent to the Children's Gallery. That room and the rear corridor were used as display areas. A small percentage of exhibition space was allotted for the interior display cubicles.
In 1968 the Art Rental Gallery was moved again to galleries 48 and 49. At this time the interior designer cubicles were discontinued. In the spring of 1969, an exhibition of designer furniture shared the principle exhibition area with rental paintings. In the late spring of 1969, the gallery was moved to the front of the building and occupied two rooms, which at one time comprised the Membership and Development office. The gallery remained at this location until its closing in 1973.
The Board of Trustees decided in January 1973 to discontinue the Art Rental Gallery due to high operating costs. With the increase in private galleries in Washington, the Board felt that the members and public had an increased availability to all aspects of art patronage, and that the Art Rental Gallery had served its purpose of "introducing" Washingtonians to current American art and promoting Washington area artists. The Board consensus was that the Corcoran Gallery of Art would continue to encourage Washington artists by exhibitions of their works in the galleries and corridors, and that the Corcoran staff would always be willing to advise members who wished to know about artists and galleries in Washington.
Custodial History
These records were transferred to the Corcoran Archives from storage in 1980.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Art Rental and Sales Gallery include consignments with commercial galleries and individual artists, master contracts, prospective artists, inventories and shipping lists, correspondence, rental procedures, administrative information and operating procedures, financial reports, insurance, legal information and suits, rental applications and agreements, and Gallery income from rentals and sales. The dates of material range from beginning to end of the Gallery's operation, from 1962 to 1973.
These records reflect the Art Rental Gallery's growth and document its rental and sales activity, covering all aspects of the operation of the gallery, from administrative concerns to operating procedures. The records also reflect the currents of modern taste and the trends in art through the sixties and early seventies.
Several well-known and established artists were chosen from commercial galleries in New York to exhibit in the Art Rental Gallery. Among these are Andy Warhol, Roy Lichtenstein, Leonard Baskin, and Josef Albers. Washington area artists were also chosen for exhibition in the gallery for rental or purchase.
Persons who figure prominently in the records are Inga Wall Heck, Julie Forgey Lea, Judith Lanius, and Cecelia Kramer.
The records are not continuous, and there are notable gaps in the administrative and financial information.
Separated Materials
According to the Corcoran Archives legacy guides, during the initial processing the following materials were removed and placed in more appropriate locations:
Newsclippings moved to Artist vertical files or history clipping files; Announcements and invitations moved to Special Events ephemera files; Photos moved to Archives audio-visual records or Artists vertical files.
Art; Artists; Museums; Washington (D.C.)
- Consignments, 1962-1973; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Organized into 5 subseries: Prospective artists, Artists and galleries represented in the ARG, Commercial galleries, Individual artists, and Summary report on art rented.
  - Prospective artists, 1962-1973; Series 1 Subseries 1
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains correspondence between the Art Rental Gallery and artists who were potential exhibitors with the ARG.
    - Prospective Artists, Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 1)
  - Artists and galleries represented in the ARG, 1962-1969; Series 1 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains dated lists of artists, both individual and those represented by commercial galleries, and the titles of their works, that were represented in the ARG for a given year. There is not a complete run of lists from the opening of the ARG to its close.
    - Artists and Galleries Represented in the Corcoran Rental Gallery, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 2)
  - Commerical galleries, 1962-1973; Series 1 Subseries 3
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by gallery.
    This subseries contains general correspondence, master contracts between the commercial galleries and the ARG, consignment lists, receipts, invoices and shipping lists, expired contracts, and lists of works either sold or returned to the galleries.
    - Alan Gallery, 1961 October 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 3)
    - Amel Gallery, 1962 October 09-1966 April 29; Series 1, Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 4)
    - Artist Studio, 1969 March 01-1970 April 03; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 5)
    - Artist's Mart, 1962 March 22; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 6)
    - Associated Artists Gallery, 1962 February 02-1962 March 27; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 7)
    - Babcock Gallery, 1961 October 30-1972 March 23; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 8-10)
    - Franz Bader Gallery, 1962 January 31-1973 February 14; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 11-14)
    - Banfer Gallery, 1962 September 24-1965 November 11; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 15)
    - Bianchini Gallery, 1961 November 1-1969 December 13; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 16)
    - Grace Borgenicht Gallery, 1961 October 30-1970 April 24; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 17-18)
    - C and D Edition, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 19)
    - Castelli Graphics, 1961 October 30-1971 June 02; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 20)
    - Collectors Press, 1967 April 20-1967 August 03; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 21)
    - Contemporaries, 1961 October 30-1966 September 20; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 22)
    - Daniel Corder and Michael Warren Gallery, 1961 October 30-1961 November 02; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 23)
    - Sally Cox (consultant and representative for artists), 1962 October 31-1963 August 20; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 24)
    - Dintenfass Gallery, 1961 November 06-1964 October 06; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 25)
    - The Downtown Gallery, 1963 September 13-1963 September 21; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 26)
    - Dwan Gallery, 1969 October 14; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 27)
    - East Hampton Gallery, 1964 March 19-1972 July 31; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 28)
    - Robert Elkon Gallery, 1963 September 20-1964 October 08; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 29)
    - Andre Emmerick Gallery, 1961 October 30-1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 30)
    - Richard Feigen Gallery, Inc., 1965 November 03-1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 31-33)
    - Feingarten Galleries, 1962-January 15-1966 August 27; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 34)
    - Fendrick Gallery, 1964 January 23-1972 December 29; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 35-37)
    - Fischbach Gallery, 1967 October 06-1972 August 21; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 38)
    - Fontana Gallery, 1963 February 12-1963 March 05; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 39)
    - The Forum Gallery, 1961 October 30-1964 October 06; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 40)
    - Gallery One, 1963 January 04-1963 February 07; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 41)
    - Graham Gallery, 1962 January 12-1966 January 26; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 42)
    - Grand Gallery, 1964 September 22; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 43)
    - Graphics International, 1973 May 01-1973 June 06; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 44)
    - Jane Haslem Gallery, 1970 December 20-1972 August 27; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 45)
    - Henri Gallery, 1962 November 02-1972 December 28; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 46)
    - Highgate Gallery, 1962 November; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 47)
    - Hirschl and Adler Gallery, 1965 November 04-1966 October 15; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 48)
    - Hom Gallery, 1971 December 09-1972 December 22; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 49)
    - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1963 September 17-1974 December 18; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 50-52)
    - Jefferson Place Gallery, 1962 April 24-1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 53)
    - June I Gallery, 1971 November 30-1973 March 15; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 54)
    - Kennedy Galleries, 1965 September 28; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 55)
    - Kornblee Gallery, 1961 October 31-1966 September 28; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 56)
    - Kraushaar Gallery, 1961 January 12-1973 February 16; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 57-58)
    - Felix Landau Gallery, 1966 September 23-1970 September 24; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 59)
    - Larcada Gallery, 1966 September 23; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 60)
    - Lunn Gallery, 1969 November 14-1973 March 12; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 61-62)
    - Gallery Marc, 1972 February 17-1972 May 18; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 63)
    - Mi Chou Gallery, 1963 September 21-1972 January 19; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 64)
    - Mickelson Gallery, 1964 May 11-1975 January 23; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 65)
    - Midtown Galleries, 1961 October 31-1972 March 21; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 66-67)
    - Multiples Gallery, 1969 March 31-1972 October 25; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 68)
    - Nessler Gallery, 1962 February 02-1965 November 10; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 69)
    - Nordness Gallery, 1962 January 17-1972 September 02; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folders 70-71)
    - Osborne Gallery, 1964 September 11-1966 September 06; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 72)
    - Betty Parsons Gallery, 1967 October 09-1973 January 29; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 73)
    - Peridot Gallery, 1964 September 11-1966 October 29; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 74)
    - Poindexter Gallery, 1962 January 10-1973 February 16; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 75)
    - Protech-Ruikin, 1970 June 06-1972 February 09; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 76)
    - Pyramid Galleries, 1969 October 14-1973 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 77)
    - The Royal Athena II Gallery, 1964 September 01-1964 October 05; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 78)
    - Lawrence Rubin Gallery, 1972 May 09-1973 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 79)
    - Sach's Gallery, 1965 September 23-1972 April 14; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 80)
    - Saint Armand's Gallery, 1973 March 26; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 81)
    - Bertha Schaeffer Gallery, 1962 November 01-1972 March 20; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 82)
    - Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, 1968 December 06-1972 May 11; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.001, Folder 83)
    - Schuster Gallery, 1966 April 26-1972 March 21; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 1)
    - Siegel Gallery, 1972 October 17-1973 February 13; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 2)
    - Sindelir Gallery, undated; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 3)
    - Staempfli Gallery, 1964 September 10-1966 November 01; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 4)
    - Allen Stone Gallery, 1964 September 03-1965 October 14; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 5)
    - Studio Gallery, 1965 October 07-1971 April 07; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 6)
    - Esther Stuttman Gallery, 1965 April 23; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 7)
    - Tapestry Associates, 1970 December 02-1971 June 24; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 8)
    - Tibor DeNagy Gallery, 1962 September 20-1966 September 28; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 9)
    - Washington Gallery, 1962 March 09-1963 April 28; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 10)
    - World House Galleries, 1961 December 05-1962 September 09; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 11)
    - Workshop Gallery, 1970 September 19-1971 may 21; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 12)
  - Individual artists, 1962-1973; Series 1 Subseries 4
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the artist's surname.
    This subseries contains correspondence, consignments lists, master contracts, invoices and receipts, shipping lists, lists of returned or sold items, and rejection letters.
    Separated Materials
    Certain biographical and promotional material on the artists has been removed to the artist vertical file.
    - Abelow, Paula, 1971 December 20-1973 January 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 13)
    - Abraham, Mrs. Rachel, 1972 February 01, 1972 February 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 14)
    - Acheson, Alice, 1969 April 11-1973 February 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 15)
    - Adler, Lee, 1968 November 22-1975 June 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 16)
    - Alu, Barbara, 1972 January 02 and 1972 February 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 17)
    - Appleman, Dale, 1972 May 05-1973 September 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 18)
    - Arneson, R. Gordon, 1970 September 19-1971 November 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 19)
    - ASCAIN, 1973 February 02, 1973 February 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 20)
    - Barnett, Thomas M., 1970 September 18, 1972 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 21)
    - Benson, Ann, 1970 September 22, 1972 February 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 22)
    - Benson, Pat, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 23)
    - Berkowitz, Leon, 1967 June 06-1978 June 21; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 24)
    - Bernadin, Maren, 1970 September 18-1978 November 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 25)
    - Berns, Ben, 1968 November 19-1971 January 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 26)
    - Bienen, Susan, 1972 January 02-1973 May 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 27)
    - Bookatz, Sam, 1963 May 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 28)
    - Bottomley, Sue Anne, 1971 June 16, 1971 December 06; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 29)
    - Boulard, Coette, 1972 February 02-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 30)
    - Branson, Otho, 1971 December 07, 1972 August 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 31)
    - Brent, Barbara, 1970 December 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 32)
    - Bridge, Allan, 1970 September 17, 1972 February 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 33)
    - Brillant, Gilou, 1971 November 11-1978 November 17; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 34)
    - Brown, Aurelia, 1965 January 27-1966 February 24; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 35)
    - Bujese, Arlene, 1970 May 26-1973 July 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 36)
    - Byerly, Radford, 1973 January 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 37)
    - Callner, Richard, 1971 May 18-1972 January 21; Series 1 Subsseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 38)
    - Cafritz, Elaine, 1969 November 14-1972 February 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 39)
    - Carter, Clarence H., 1969 September 11-1972 March 09; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 40)
    - Carter, John R., 1969 April 04-1972 January 14; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 41)
    - Christienberry, Bill, 1970 November 04-1972 September 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 42)
    - Clark, John, 1972 December 18, 1973 February 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 43)
    - Clark, Lucy, 1970 September 18-1973 March 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 44)
    - Clark, Michael, 1969 October 11-1973 February 07; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 45)
    - Clark, Thomas E., 1971 January 22-1974 July 16; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 46)
    - Claude, Kitty, 1970 April 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 47)
    - Cohen, Robert, 1972 October 31-1973 February 27; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 48)
    - Comes, Marcella, 1965 March 15; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 49)
    - Conroy, Richard Timothy, 1969 December 02-1971 December 20; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 50)
    - Consolazio, William V., 1965 April 22-1965 September; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 51)
    - Coppel, Marcia, 1970 March 18-1970 June 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 52)
    - Corkery, Timothy, 1965 October-1966 June 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 53)
    - Crouch, Miller, 1972 June 18-1973 February 26; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 54)
    - Corvello, William, 1969 October 07-1973 March 05; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 55)
    - Cusick, Nancy, 1970 March 18-1970 June 19; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 56)
    - Davis, Albert, 1964 December 03-1965 March 30; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 57)
    - Davis, Martina, 1971 September 17-1972 April 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 58)
    - De Butler, Jacqueline, 1973 March 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 59)
    - De Launey, Sonia, 1972 November 13-1972 December 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 60)
    - De Looper, Willem, 1970 October 08, 1971 December 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 61)
    - Dine, Jim, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 62)
    - Downey, Juan, 1969 January 02-1972 August 29; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 63)
    - Dreyer, Luba, 1971 September 14-1973 February 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 64)
    - Drummond, Sally, 1972 November 18-1973 January 01; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 65)
    - Dutterer, William, 1969 December 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 66)
    - Edelman, Ann, 1969 November 14-1973 April 04; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 67)
    - Espenshade, Laurence, 1971 July 27-1972 August 24; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 68)
    - Ferguson, Suzanne, 1970 November 20-1973 April 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 69)
    - Frank, Jane, 1962 February 06-1962 June 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 70)
    - Freese, Marjorie, 1969 November 14-1971 February 18; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 71)
    - Glassman, Audrey, 1970 April 02, 1971 February 23; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 72)
    - Glover, Lessie, 1972 March 03-1974 October 05; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 73)
    - Goding, Rose, 1970 May 27-1973 February 08; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 74)
    - Goldberg, Michael, 1969 November 13-1974 July 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 75)
    - Golden, Pat, 1969 November 14-1978 December 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 76)
    - Gracian, Astchik, 1970 April 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 77)
    - Grady, Ruby, 1969 November 05-1973 February 28; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 78)
    - Green, Robert, 1969 November 14-1973 March 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 79)
    - Greenly, Colin, 1972 August 11-1976 May 05; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 80)
    - Gregory, Lawra, 1972 May 08, 1972 June 13; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 81)
    - Griffin, Cornelius, 1965 April 03; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder data_value_missing_bcae0340972f6fe3a4c332d341323b65)
    - Guernsey, John, 1970 September 18-1972 March 22; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 82)
    - Hakumaki, 1971 June 12; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 83)
    - Halem, Judi and Henry, 1965 June 02; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box RG3.1-1998.002, Folder 84)